Introduce the challenge: crowding and long wait times on ma...
Address trade-offs, including temporary construction disrup...
Narration for beat_008, beat_009
Close with what commuters should watch in the next quarter
Show measurable improvements in delay minutes and rider thr...
Narration for beat_017, beat_018
Address trade-offs, including temporary construction disrup...
Explain what changed after schedule optimization and signal...
Introduce the challenge: crowding and long wait times on ma...
Narration for beat_028, beat_029, beat_030
Close with what commuters should watch in the next quarter
Explain what changed after schedule optimization and signal...
Narration for beat_044, beat_045
Introduce the challenge: crowding and long wait times on ma...
Address trade-offs, including temporary construction disrup...
Narration for beat_053, beat_054
Close with what commuters should watch in the next quarter
Show measurable improvements in delay minutes and rider thr...
Explain what changed after schedule optimization and signal...
Narration for beat_064, beat_065, beat_066
Introduce the challenge: crowding and long wait times on ma...
Show measurable improvements in delay minutes and rider thr...
Narration for beat_080, beat_081
Explain what changed after schedule optimization and signal...
Close with what commuters should watch in the next quarter
Narration for beat_089, beat_090